Frost Is Not The Only Thing That Bites In the Snow!
Wrong Turn 4: Bloody Beginnings is a horror,
thriller film directed by Declan O'Brien.
A group of friends take refuge in a deserted sanatorium
after they are left stranded in a snowstorm.
Later, the place becomes a death trap when man-eating cannibals surround them.
Kenia, played by Jennifer Pudavick.
Sara, played by Tenika Davis.
Jenna, played by Terra Vnesa.
Dr. Annmarie McQuaid, played by Kristen Harris.
Bridget, played by Kaitlyn Leeb.
Daniel, played by Dean Armstrong.
Wrong Turn 4: Bloody Beginnings is a 2011 slasher film
written and directed by Declan O'Brien.
It is the fourth installment of the Wrong Turn film series and served as
the first part of a prequel to the Wrong Turn (2003).
Starring Jennifer Pudavick, Tenika Davis, Kaitlyn Wong, and Terra Vnesa, the film follows a group of college students who get lost in a storm
during a snowmobile trip and take shelter in an abandoned sanatorium that, unbeknownst to them, is home to deformed cannibals.
Wrong Turn 4: Bloody Beginnings was released to DVD and Blu-ray on
October 25, 2011, by 20th Century Fox Home Entertainment.
The film was not well-received by critics upon release with fans having a
mixed reception and had grossed $3.6 million in home sales.
It was followed by Wrong Turn 5: Bloodlines (2012).
The film explores themes of motel, forest, west
virginia, lesbian relationship, murder.
The tone is dark and intense.